Ken Jeong: You Complete Me, Ho is a comedy,
documentary film directed by Jon M. Chu.
In his first-ever stand-up special, Ken Jeong shares hilarious stories from his
Hollywood career -- and reveals how "The Hangover" saved his life.
Self, played by Ken Jeong.
Kendrick Kang-Joh Jeong ( JUNG; Korean: 정강조; born July 13,
1969) is an American stand-up comedian and actor.
He rose to prominence for playing Leslie Chow in The Hangover film series
(2009–2013) and Ben Chang in the NBC sitcom Community (2009–2015).
He created, wrote and produced the ABC sitcom Dr.
Ken (2015–2017), in which he portrays the titular character, and he has appeared in the films Knocked Up (2007), Role
Models (2008), Furry Vengeance (2010), The Duff (2015), Ride Along 2 (2016), Crazy Rich Asians (2018), Scoob!
(2020), Tom & Jerry (2021), and KPop Demon Hunters (2025).
Jeong is a licensed physician in California but has since
stopped practicing in favor of his acting career.
He appears as a panelist on the American version of the singing competition show The
Masked Singer and appeared on the first series of the British version.
He also serves as the host of I Can See Your Voice.
The tone is lighthearted.